SIMI PANDEY





Professional Summary

I can very well for implement a fund's investment strategy and managing its trading activities and 7+ years of experience seeks to improve overall efficiency at your Office, communicative financial analyst, specializing in informative and persuasive financial presentations, cost accounting, and team management. Degree in Finance and two related certifications from the Corporate Finance Institute



Phone:

08102596147

Email:

simmipandey0202@gmail.c om

Address:

Bed College Road, Jamshedpur, 831019 (IN)



Employment History

Mutual fund manager , GIIS. Jamshedpur, Jharkhand Jun. 2018 - May. 2023

implementing a fund's investment strategy and managing its trading activities. They oversee mutual funds or pensions, manage analysts, conduct research, and make important investment decisions

advanced portfolio management, dividend reinvestment, risk reduction, convenience, and fair pricing.

Director , My ambition institute . Jamshedpur , Jharkhand Apr. 2012 - Jun. 2017

Determining the company's strategic objectives and policies. Monitoring progress towards achieving the objectives and policies. Appointing senior management. Accounting for the company's activities to relevant parties, eg shareholders.

Skills

Leadership

strategizing

Crm

Sales manager , Nippon life insurance. Jamshedpur , Jharkhand

May. 2008 - Jun. 2011

Goal-setting responsibilities. ...

Training and development. ...

Administrative tasks. ...

Team and individual organization. ...

hiring employees, determining the need for training and delivering it, coaching sales representatives, and establishing sales territory

Credit card manager , Citi bank. Jamshedpur, Jharkhand

Feb. 2005 - Feb. 2010

Researching and evaluating clients' creditworthiness. Creating credit scoring models to predict risks. Approving or rejecting loan requests, based on credibility and potential revenues and losses.



Education

Odisha college of studies, Bhubneshwar, Orrissa

Graduation, Finance and marketing, Feb. 2004

Vidya bharti chinmaya vidyala, Jamshedpur, Jharkhand

High School Diploma, Computer science, Feb. 2000